Guide to the Yale Athletics Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale athletics photographs
1850-2007
RU 691
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
108.93
(99 boxes)
The materials consist of photographs of Yale athletic events, associations and facilities. Included are shots of practices, teams, individual athletes, cheerleaders, and games. Also included are posters, lithographs and engravings from nineteenth-century magazines. Baseball, crew, football, swimming, and track are particularly well documented.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-C (YRG 38-C), Audiovisual materials and memorabilia documenting athletics at Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Access to Accession 2008-A-065 is by appointment only. Contact the Head of Public Services or the Public Services Manager.
Arrangement
The pictures are arranged by sport, thereunder chronologically and in subsequent accessions.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs of Yale athletic events, associations and facilities. Included are shots of practices, teams, individual athletes, cheerleaders, and games. Also included are posters, lithographs and engravings from nineteenth-century magazines. Baseball, crew, football, swimming, and track are particularly well documented.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Accession 2017-A-060 gift of Anne Hall Connor, 2017.
Baseball; College athletes; College sports; Football; Rowing; Swimming; Track and field; Slides (photographs); Engravings (prints); Lithographs; Photographs; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Sports; Yale University Athletic Association; Yale University -- Baseball; Yale University -- Football; Yale University -- Rowing; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University -- Swimming; Yale University -- Track and field; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
- Pictures of Yale athletics, circa 1850-2000; Series I
  - Photographs
    - All Sports [see also oversize and folio]
      - 1889 (Box 30, Folder 250)
      - 1896 (Box 30, Folder 250)
      - 1897 Captains (Box 30, Folder 250)
      - 1897, freshman (Box 30, Folder 250)
      - Captains 1898, 1901, 1907, 1910, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 251)
      - Captains 1916, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - 1925 Yale Daily News (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - 1931 (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - Captains 1931 (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - 1932 (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - 1981 Yale football (Magazine) w/ other sports photos (Box 30, Folder 252)
      - Unidentified: Captain (Box 30, Folder 252)
    - Baseball [see also oversize and folio]
      - 1869 (Box 19, Folder 170)
      - 1871 (Box 19, Folder 170)
      - circa 1872 (Box 19, Folder 170)
      - 1874 (Box 19, Folder 171)
      - 1874 (Box 19, Folder 171)
      - 1875 (Box 19, Folder 171)
      - 1875 (Box 19, Folder 172)
      - 1876 (Box 19, Folder 172)
      - 1877 (Box 19, Folder 172)
      - 1878 (Box 19, Folder 173)
      - circa 1878 (Box 19, Folder 173)
      - 1879 (Box 19, Folder 173)
      - 1880 (Box 20, Folder 174)
      - 1881 (Box 20, Folder 174)
      - 1881 (Box 20, Folder 174)
      - 1882 (Box 20, Folder 175)
      - 1883 (Box 20, Folder 176)
      - 1883, freshman (Box 20, Folder 177)
      - 1884 (Box 20, Folder 177)
      - 1885 (Box 20, Folder 178)
      - 1885 (Box 20, Folder 178)
      - 1886 (Box 20, Folder 179)
      - 1886, freshman (Box 20, Folder 180)
      - 1887 (Box 21, Folder 181)
      - 1887, freshman (Box 21, Folder 181)
      - 1888 (Box 21, Folder 182)
      - 1888, freshman (Box 21, Folder 182)
      - 1889 (Box 21, Folder 183)
      - 1890 (Box 21, Folder 183)
      - 1891 (Box 21, Folder 184)
      - 1891, freshman (Box 21, Folder 184)
      - circa 1891 (Box 21, Folder 184)
      - 1892 (Box 21, Folder 185)
      - 1892, freshman (Box 21, Folder 185)
      - 1893 (Box 21, Folder 185)
      - 1893 Spalding Cup (Box 21, Folder 185)
      - 1894 (Box 21, Folder 186)
      - 1894, freshman (Box 21, Folder 186)
      - 1894, individual portraits (Box 21, Folder 186)
      - 1895 (Box 21, Folder 187)
      - 1895, freshman (Box 21, Folder 187)
      - circa 1895 (Box 21, Folder 187)
      - 1896 (Box 21, Folder 187)
      - 1897 (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - 1897, freshman (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - 1898 (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - 1898 (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - 1898, freshman (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - 1899 (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - 1899 Non-Yale (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - 1900 (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - 1901 (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - 1902 (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - 1903 (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - 1904 (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - 1904 (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - 1905 (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - 1905, freshman (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - 1906 (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - 1907 (Box 22, Folder 192)
      - 1907, freshman (Box 22, Folder 192)
      - 1908 (Box 22, Folder 192)
      - circa 1908, individual portraits (Box 22, Folder 192)
      - 1909 (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - 1909 Non-Yale (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - 1910 (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - 1910 Yale Daily News, Harvard-Yale Game (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - 1910 Unidentified: Team Portraits (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - 1911 (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1912 (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1912, individual portraits (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1913 (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1914 (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1914 Unidentified: Team Portraits, Game Photo (Box 22, Folder 194)
      - 1915 (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - 1915, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - 1916 (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - 1916, action (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - circa 1916 (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - 1917 (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - 1917, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - 1918 (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - 1919 (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - 1919, freshman (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - circa 1919 (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - 1921 (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - 1922 (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - 1922, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - 1923 (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1924 (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1924, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1925-1928 (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1928, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1929-1931 (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - circa 1931 (Box 23, Folder 198)
      - 1932 (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1933 (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1934 (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1934, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - circa 1934 (Box 23, Folder 199)
      - 1935, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - circa 1935 (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1936 (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1936, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1937 (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1937, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1939 (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1939, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1940, action (Box 23, Folder 200)
      - 1941 (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1941, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1942-1944 (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1948-1951 (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1955-1959 (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1960 (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1960, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1960, action (Box 23, Folder 201)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 202)
      - circa 1963, individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 202)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 202)
      - 1967, action (Box 23, Folder 202)
      - Unidentified (Box 23, Folder 203)
      - Team Portraits (Box 23, Folder 203)
      - Unidentified (Box 24, Folder 204)
      - Team Portraits (Box 24, Folder 204)
      - Individual Portraits (Box 24, Folder 204)
      - Action (Box 24, Folder 204)
      - Graduate club team Portraits (Box 24, Folder 204)
    - Basketball
      - 1898-1903 (Box 24, Folder 205)
      - 1904 (Box 24, Folder 206)
      - 1904, freshman (Box 24, Folder 206)
      - 1905 (Box 24, Folder 206)
      - circa 1905 (Box 24, Folder 206)
      - 1905, freshman (Box 24, Folder 206)
      - 1906 (Box 24, Folder 207)
      - circa 1906 (Box 24, Folder 207)
      - 1906, freshman (Box 24, Folder 207)
      - 1907-1911 (Box 24, Folder 207)
      - 1913 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1915 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1916 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1916, freshman (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1919-1921 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1926, freshman (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1927, freshman (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1929 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - 1931-1932 (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1933 (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1935 (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1937, individual portraits (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 24, Folder 209)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - 1945 (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - 1953 (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - circa 1964 (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - Unidentified (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - Team Portraits (Box 24, Folder 210)
      - Action (Box 24, Folder 210)
    - Bicycling
      - circa 1891 (Box 31, Folder 255)
    - Boxing [see also folio]
      - 1920 Yale and MIT (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1921 (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1923 (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1933 (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1934 (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 25, Folder 217)
      - 1948 (Box 25, Folder 218)
      - 1953 (Box 25, Folder 218)
      - circa 1953 (Box 25, Folder 218)
      - circa 1955 (Box 25, Folder 218)
    - Cheerleaders [see also oversize]
      - 1912 (Box 30, Folder 253)
      - 1916 (Box 30, Folder 253)
      - 1920 (Box 30, Folder 253)
      - 1931 (Box 30, Folder 253)
      - 1969 (Box 30, Folder 253)
      - Unidentified (Box 30, Folder 253)
    - Crew [see also oversize and folio]
      - 1859 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1861 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - circa 1864 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1864 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1865 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1866 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1869 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1870 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1873 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1874 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1874 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1875 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1875 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1876 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1876 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1876 Junior Team in 1874 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1877 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1877, freshman (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1877 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - 1878 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - circa 1878 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1878 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1879 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1879 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1880 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1880, freshman (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 1881 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 1881 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - circa 1881-1884, varsity? (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - 1882 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1883 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1883, freshman (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1883 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1884 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1884 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - circa 1884 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 1885 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 1886 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - 1886 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - 1887 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - 1887, freshman (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - 1888 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - 1889 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - 1889 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - 1890 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - 1890 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - 1890 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - 1891 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - circa 1891 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - 1891, freshman (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - 1892 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - 1892 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - 1893 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - 1893 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - 1894 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - 1894, freshman (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Pre-1895 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - 1895 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - 1895 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - 1895, freshman (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - 1896 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - 1896 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - 1897 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - 1897 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - 1897, freshman (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - 1898 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - 1898, freshman (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - 1898 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - 1899 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - 1899 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - 1900 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - 1900, individual portraits (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - 1900 Candidates (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - 1900, freshman (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - 1901 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - 1901 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - 1901, individual portraits (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - 1902 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - 1902, freshman (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Julian Curtiss, Advisory Coach 1902-1911 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - 1903 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - circa 1903 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - 1903 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - 1904 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - 1904, individual portraits (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - 1905 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - 1905, freshman (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - 1906 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - 1906 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - 1907 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - 1907, freshman (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - 1908 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - 1909 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - circa 1909 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - 1909-1910 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - 1910 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - 1911 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - circa 1911 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - 1912 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - 1912-1913 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - 1913 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - 1913, freshman (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - 1914 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - 1914, individual portraits (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - 1914, freshman (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - 1915 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - 1916 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - circa 1916 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - 1916, freshman (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - 1917 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - 1918 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - 1919 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - 1920 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - 1921 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - 1922 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - 1922, freshman (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - 1923 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - 1923, Junior Varsity (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - 1924 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - 1925 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - 1926? (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - 1926, freshman (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - 1928 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - 1929 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - circa 1929 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - 1930 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - 1931 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - 1932 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - 1932, Junior Varsity (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - 1933 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - 1934 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - 1934, Junior Varsity (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - 1934 Coaches Conference (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - 1935 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - 1935, Junior Varsity (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - circa 1935 assorted snapshots (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - 1936 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - 1937 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - 1937 Derby Day on Housatonic River, Derby, CT (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - 1937, intramural (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - 1938 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - 1939 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - 1940 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - 1940, Junior Varsity (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - 1940, intramural (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - 1941, Junior Varsity (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - 1942, freshman (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - 1946 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - 1947 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - 1953 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - 1954 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - 1955 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - 1956 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - 1958 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - 1961 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - 1965 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - 1967 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - 1980, individual portraits- Women's Crew (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Unidentified: (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Team Portraits (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Action (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Unidentified: (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Action (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Boathouse Scenes (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - [Coaches] (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Unidentified: (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Indoor training (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Captain (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Freshman, action (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Undated Class, action (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Intramural (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Spectators (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Unidentified: (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Trophy (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Cartoon (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Non-Yale (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Department of athletics [see also oversize]
      - Official football Photographer, circa 1930-circa 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Yale-Harvard, Oxford-Cambridge combined track teams, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Undergraduate Athletic Association, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Undergraduate Athletic Association, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Yale Track team [before clash with Oxford-Cambridge], 1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Keith Brown [Yale track] in Britain, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - W. H. Neale, Director of, intramural Sports, 1943-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Physical Training, Personnel-Payne Whitney Gym, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Football Support Staff, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Faculty Athletics, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - George Higgins [football], undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Football Team Portrait, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Diving
      - 1937, action (Box 31, Folder 257)
      - 1942, action (Box 31, Folder 257)
      - 1970, freshman, action (Box 31, Folder 257)
      - Unidentified:, action (Box 31, Folder 257)
    - Fencing
      - 1915 (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1924 (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1935 (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1936, action (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1937, action (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1938 (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - circa 1942, action (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - 1953, action (Box 31, Folder 256)
      - Unidentified (Box 31, Folder 256)
    - Field Hockey
      - 1977, action (Box 31, Folder 269)
    - Football [see also oversize and folio]
      - 1869 (Box 9, Folder 77)
      - 1872 (Box 9, Folder 78)
      - 1873 (Box 9, Folder 78)
      - 1874 (Box 9, Folder 78)
      - 1875 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - 1876 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - 1877 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - 1878 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - 1879 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - 1880 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - circa 1880 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - 1881 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - 1881, freshman (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - 1882 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - 1883 (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - 1883, freshman (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - 1884 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - 1884, freshman (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - 1885 (Box 10, Folder 85)
      - 1886 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - 1886, freshman (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - 1887 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - 1888 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - 1888, Dinner in 1913 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - 1889 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - 1890 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - circa 1890 Harper's Weekly Illustration (Box 11, Folder 91)
      - 1891 (Box 11, Folder 92)
      - 1891 (Box 11, Folder 93)
      - 1891 20th and 35th Anniversary Dinners (Box 11, Folder 93)
      - 1892 (Box 11, Folder 94-95)
      - 1892 (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - 1892 Anniversary Dinner in [1924?] (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - 1892, individual portraits (Box 11, Folder 97)
      - 1893 (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - 1893 (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - 1894 (Box 12, Folder 99-100)
      - 1895 (Box 12, Folder 101)
      - 1895, individual portraits (Box 12, Folder 102)
      - 1895, freshman (Box 12, Folder 102)
      - 1896 (Box 12, Folder 103)
      - 1896, individual portraits (Box 12, Folder 103)
      - 1896, freshman (Box 12, Folder 103)
      - 1896 (Box 12, Folder 104)
      - 1897 (Box 12, Folder 104)
      - 1897, individual portraits (Box 12, Folder 104)
      - 1897, freshman (Box 12, Folder 105)
      - 1898 (Box 12, Folder 105)
      - 1898, freshman (Box 12, Folder 105)
      - 1899 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      - 1899 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      - 1900 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      - circa 1900 (Box 13, Folder 107)
      - 1901 (Box 13, Folder 108)
      - 1901 Bicentennial Team of alumni (Box 13, Folder 109)
      - 1901 (Box 13, Folder 109)
      - 1902 (Box 13, Folder 110)
      - 1903 (Box 13, Folder 111)
      - 1904 (Box 13, Folder 111)
      - 1904, freshman (Box 13, Folder 111)
      - 1905 (Box 13, Folder 112)
      - 1905 (Box 13, Folder 113)
      - 1905 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      - 1906 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      - circa 1906, action (Box 14, Folder 114)
      - 1907 (Box 14, Folder 115)
      - 1907, freshman (Box 14, Folder 115)
      - 1908 (Box 14, Folder 116)
      - 1909 (Box 14, Folder 117-120)
      - circa 1910 (Box 15, Folder 121)
      - 1911 (Box 15, Folder 121)
      - 1912 (Box 15, Folder 121)
      - circa 1912 (Box 15, Folder 122)
      - 1913 (Box 15, Folder 122)
      - 1913 (Box 15, Folder 122)
      - 1914 (Box 15, Folder 123)
      - 1915 (Box 15, Folder 123)
      - 1916 (Box 15, Folder 124)
      - 1916, freshman (Box 15, Folder 124)
      - 1917 (Box 15, Folder 124)
      - 1918 (Box 15, Folder 125)
      - 1918 (Box 15, Folder 125)
      - 1919 (Box 15, Folder 125)
      - 1919, freshman (Box 15, Folder 125a)
      - 1920 (Box 15, Folder 125a)
      - 1920, freshman (Box 15, Folder 125a)
      - 1920 (Box 15, Folder 126)
      - 1921 (Box 15, Folder 126)
      - 1922 (Box 15, Folder 126)
      - 1923 (Box 16, Folder 127)
      - 1923, individual portraits (Box 16, Folder 127)
      - 1923, Reunions, 1957, 1961, undated (Box 16, Folder 127)
      - 1924 (Box 16, Folder 128)
      - 1925 (Box 16, Folder 128)
      - 1925 (Box 16, Folder 128)
      - 1926 (Box 16, Folder 129)
      - 1926, freshman (Box 16, Folder 129)
      - 1927 (Box 16, Folder 129)
      - 1928 (Box 16, Folder 130)
      - 1929 (Box 16, Folder 130)
      - 1929 (Box 16, Folder 130)
      - 1930 (Box 16, Folder 131)
      - circa 1930, Line Coach Adam Walsh (Box 16, Folder 132)
      - 1931 (Box 16, Folder 132)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 16, Folder 132)
      - circa 1931 Albie Booth and Ripley (Box 16, Folder 133)
      - 1932 (Box 16, Folder 133)
      - 1932, 150 lb. (Box 16, Folder 133)
      - 1933 (Box 16, Folder 134)
      - 1933, individual portraits (Box 16, Folder 134)
      - circa 1933, individual portraits (Box 16, Folder 134)
      - 1933, 150 lb. (Box 16, Folder 135)
      - 1933, freshman, individual portraits (Box 16, Folder 135)
      - 1934 (Box 16, Folder 135)
      - 1934, 150 lb. (Box 16, Folder 136)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 16, Folder 136)
      - 1934, intramural (Box 16, Folder 136)
      - 1935 (Box 16, Folder 137)
      - 1936 (Box 16, Folder 137)
      - 1937 (Box 16, Folder 137)
      - 1937, freshman (Box 16, Folder 138)
      - 1938 (Box 16, Folder 138)
      - 1938, Junior Varsity (Box 16, Folder 138)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 17, Folder 139)
      - 1939 (Box 17, Folder 139)
      - 1940 (Box 17, Folder 139)
      - 1941 (Box 17, Folder 140)
      - 1942 (Box 17, Folder 140)
      - 1942, freshman (Box 17, Folder 140)
      - 1943 (Box 17, Folder 141)
      - 1944 (Box 17, Folder 141)
      - 1944, Alumna fund Association Annual Report (Box 17, Folder 141)
      - 1944?, action (Box 17, Folder 142)
      - 1945 (Box 17, Folder 142)